

# **SAMUKELE NDLOVU**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, WEB DESIGNER

### CONTACT



**(**) 072 395 8208



samukele107@gmail.com

### **PROFILE**

I am a software developer with a passion for building high-quality software applications. I have more than 3 years of experience in the field, I am well-versed in software development methodologies such as Agile and Scrum. I enjoy playing computer games and travelling.

## PROGRAMMING SKILLS

HTML & CSS. Python. Diango Bootstrap. Javascript. Angular. Wordpress.

# Other Skills Include

Performance Optimization. Installing and configuring computer hardware and software.

Monitoring and maintaining computer systems and networks. Troubleshooting and Quality Control.

## **EDUCATION**

Matric - 2015

Hyperiondev - Software Engineering (2022-2023)

Udemy - Python for Data Science and Machine Learning

CodeX - Attended 2 weeks bootcamp on Javascript

Freecodecamp (online) - Basic CSS, HTML, JAVASCRIPT, and Python Programming(2020-2021)

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Company: A1 Group

Sales Agent (2018 - 2021)

**Technical Support Agent (2022 - current)** 

My role include providing Technical services to clients, I am responsible in assisting clients with technical issues and providing effective troubleshooting steps , which may include use of diagnostic tools and softwares. I also log client queries and complaints.

# Company: Eventar (eventar.co.za)

Web developer, Product Architecture (2021 - current

I am part of the creative team that developed Eventar. A platform where all event vendors showcase their work to customers all in one platform. My role include updating & maintaining of the website and Designing on layout

# **August Roots Healthcare**

Web developer(Part-time: 2022 - current)

I provide maintainance to the Website and updating layouts of the Website

### CONTACT

**(**) 072 395 8208

samukele107@gmail.com

# SAMUKELE NDLOVU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, WEB DESIGNER

I am a self-taught software developer with a strong passion for coding and problem-solving. My love for technology started at a young age, and I have spent countless hours studying programming languages, practicing coding challenges, and building personal projects.

Although I don't have a traditional computer science degree, I have developed a deep understanding of programming concepts and best practices through my self-study and i have furthered my knowlegde and skills through bootcamps and have rewarded with certifications. I have experience in various programming languages such as Python and JavaScript, I am comfortable working with both front-end and back-end development frameworks.